

PROFILE

Software Engineer specializing and building skills in SQL and PL/SQL, JavaScript, and Frontend development with React.js framework. Backend development using Mongo DB and Node.js. Database designing and development using SQL scripting. Project Management, SCRUM and Agile Methodology implementation using Atlassian Software.

CONTACT

PHONE: **0814818769**

EMAIL:

sibalatanics@outlook.com

LINKEDIN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/carlossibalatani-106963160/

HOBBIES

Programming
Basketball
Building computers
Tech research
Working out

SIBALATANI CARLOS SISAMU

Computer Scientist (Software Engineer)

EDUCATION

React Nano Degree, Udacity (Certificate) 2021 Complete Node.js Developer Course (Certificate) 2021 The Complete React Developer Course (Certificate) 2021

Bachelor of Computer Science in Software Development Namibia's University of Science and Technology 2016 – 2019

Degree Obtained with a 3.3 GPA, Best performing 1^{st} year student in 2016 and the best performing student in 3^{rd} year 2018

Caprivi Senior Secondary School (High school) 2009-2013

WORK EXPERIENCE (4 YEARS)

Ministry of Health and Social Services – Junior Data Analyst/Software Engineer

As a junior data analyst and software developer at MOHSS, I provide support and development on the different health systems provided by the ministry. I work with the following technologies: OpenMRS, Java and JavaScript, MySQL Databases, Node.JS with Express as well server admin using Linux systems. In addition to this, I work on hosting the ministry's systems using Ubuntu with Nginx and Apache web servers

Silnam IT Solutions – Associate Software Engineer 02/2020 – 01/2021

Silnam IT Solutions – Trainee Software Engineer 03/2019 – 02/2020

Silnam IT Solutions – Software Engineering Intern 10/2018 – 03/2019

Elev8 Consulting – Software Developer Intern 07/2018 – 10/2018

SKILLS

